JULIAN CAMERON FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

www.juliancameron.se juliancameron79@gmail.com

Tegvägen 26, 175 53 Jarfalla

PROFILE

In 2017, I upped sticks with my family and moved to Sweden from the UK, where I had a successful career in the financial sector for over 10 years. Coming to Sweden, I had the opportunity to reinvent myself and took up the challenge of learning Swedish and finding a new career path. Now I am at the beginning of what will be another successful career within web development.

EDUCATION

Code Institute — Dublin, Ireland

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development - EQF Level 5 November 2019 – January 2021

Middlesex University - London, England

Higher National Diploma in Multimedia/Graphic Design 1999 - 2001

St Charles Catholic Sixth Form College — London, England General Nation Vocational Qualification in Art and Design level one, two & three 1995 - 1999

TECHNOLOGIES

Languages: HTML, CSS, JS,

Python

Frameworks: Django, Flask,

React

Libraries: Bootstrap

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB Cloud Platforms: Heroku, AWS

SOFT SKILLS

Swedish, Teamwork, Time Management, Problem Solving, Communication, Self-Awareness, Leadership

EXPERIENCE

Production Assistant, Datasite, Merrill Corporation; London — 2005–2017

- Replied to users enquiries on product and tool features via phone, email and live chat.
- Assisted users with setup and configuration of tools and features within Datasite's technology products.
- Supported users experiencing simple or more complex issues with product or tools.
- Troubleshoot and answer user questions.
- Provided educational support on the platform's capabilities and functionality to users and colleagues.
- Built positive relationships while being proactive and anticipating users needs.
- Participated in mentoring and guidance of less experienced colleagues.

Graphic Designer, Connections Communication; London — 2002–2004

- Designed promotional material for multiple EU and local authority funded media courses.
- Led the in-house rebrand team for Connections Communication and sister company Ravenscourt Media.
- Carried out general office duties as well as assisted IT and equipment hire sections with support for students and staff. Assisted with a number of events to showcase student's work.